<?xml version="1.1" encoding="UTF-16"?>
<?xml-model href="../chapter.xsd"?>
<book name="Romans" id="45">
	<chapter num="16">
		<verse num="1">I commend unto you Phebe our sister, which is a servant of the church which is at Cenchrea:</verse>
		<verse num="2">That ye receive her in the Lord, as becometh saints, and that ye assist her in whatsoever business she hath need of you: for she hath been a succourer of many, and of myself also.</verse>
		<verse num="3">Greet Priscilla and Aquila my helpers in Christ Jesus:</verse>
		<verse num="4">Who have for my life laid down their own necks: unto whom not only I give thanks, but also all the churches of the Gentiles.</verse>
		<verse num="5">Likewise greet the church that is in their house. Salute my well-beloved Epaenetus, who is the firstfruits of Achaia unto Christ.</verse>
		<verse num="6">Greet Mary, who bestowed much labour on us.</verse>
		<verse num="7">Salute Andronicus and Junia, my kinsmen, and my fellow-prisoners, who are of note among the apostles, who also were in Christ before me.</verse>
		<verse num="8">Greet Amplias my beloved in the Lord.</verse>
		<verse num="9">Salute Urbane, our helper in Christ, and Stachys my beloved.</verse>
		<verse num="10">Salute Apelles approved in Christ. Salute them which are of Aristobulus' household.</verse>
		<verse num="11">Salute Herodion my kinsman. Greet them that be of the household of Narcissus, which are in the Lord.</verse>
		<verse num="12">Salute Tryphena and Tryphosa, who labour in the Lord. Salute the beloved Persis, which laboured much in the Lord.</verse>
		<verse num="13">Salute Rufus chosen in the Lord, and his mother and mine.</verse>
		<verse num="14">Salute Asyncritus, Phlegon, Hermas, Patrobas, Hermes, and the brethren which are with them.</verse>
		<verse num="15">Salute Philologus, and Julia, Nereus, and his sister, and Olympas, and all the saints which are with them.</verse>
		<verse num="16">Salute one another with an holy kiss. The churches of Christ salute you.</verse>
		<verse num="17">Now I beseech you, brethren, mark them which cause divisions and offences contrary to the doctrine which ye have learned; and avoid them.</verse>
		<verse num="18">For they that are such serve not our Lord Jesus Christ, but their own belly; and by good words and fair speeches deceive the hearts of the simple.</verse>
		<verse num="19">For your obedience is come abroad unto all men. I am glad therefore on your behalf: but yet I would have you wise unto that which is good, and simple concerning evil.</verse>
		<verse num="20">And the God of peace shall bruise Satan under your feet shortly. The grace of our Lord Jesus Christ be with you. Amen.</verse>
		<verse num="21">Timotheus my workfellow, and Lucius, and Jason, and Sosipater, my kinsmen, salute you.</verse>
		<verse num="22">I Tertius, who wrote this epistle, salute you in the Lord.</verse>
		<verse num="23">Gaius mine host, and of the whole church, saluteth you. Erastus the chamberlain of the city saluteth you, and Quartus a brother.</verse>
		<verse num="24">The grace of our Lord Jesus Christ be with you all. Amen.</verse>
		<verse num="25">Now to him that is of power to stablish you according to my gospel, and the preaching of Jesus Christ, according to the revelation of the mystery, which was kept secret since the world began,</verse>
		<verse num="26">But now is made manifest, and by the scriptures of the prophets, according to the commandment of the everlasting God, made known to all nations for the obedience of faith:</verse>
		<verse num="27">To God only wise, be glory through Jesus Christ for ever. Amen.</verse>
	</chapter>
</book>
